Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
A dog in the
Cambridge English Dictionary
is a domesticated
carnivorous mammal.
That's me.
Another kind of dog
is my ex-wife Tracy.
She was shagging my best mate
and business partner, Jungle.
They both were
conspiring against me.
You promised me he'd
be out of the way by now.
And he doesn't
even know about us.
Look, woman,
it's being planned.
This time next week, he'll be
a memory, a distant memory.
Now put the fucking kettle on.
Jungle
and his meathead mate
went to see the man who can.
Ex-military and long-term
friend of my family.
Terry made us untouchable.
He would clean and launder
anything Jungle and I grabbed
from shitty pawn shops
to high street banks.
Terry's relationship
with the local hunters
provided us the guns, the bikes,
and we had the dogs
bollocks to do it.
All right, Terry.
Thought I'd come and
see you, me old mate.
Oh, ain't I honored.
Ain't you just, eh?
What's wrong
with Stevie boy here?
Back to business Terry.
Got a fight next week.
I want you and
Byron there, yeah?
Okay.
Two o'clock.
Sounds good.
Usual place.
No worries.
Don't be late.
Back to your racing, Terry.
See ya there.
A week later
I arrived on my Tod.
There was no Terry; he went
bloody greyhound racing.
He'll be arriving
there right now.
Who's there to meet him then?
Dave!
The beast-master himself.
Where's the fight, Dave?
Cut the bullshit.
You stole our money.
Pleased to see you too Dave.
You on the fucking
juice again or what?
Dave always thought Byron
was ripping the firm off.
So,
who's your money on?
100 quid on Byron to win.
He'll sucker punch him
with that knuckle duster
his dad gave him.
That's his trademark,
you know that.
But what you don't know,
Dave's got a metal
plate in his jaw
from that ruck we had
with them Birmingham lads.
So, if you lose, you're
buying the Chinese and all.
We'll see!
Give me my fucking money!
When you're
lying on your hospital bed,
you don't see bright lights.
You don't see the
bloody fairies.
That's a lode of
hippie bollocks.
You just see the horrible
mangy dogs that put you there.
Two months a broken nose
and eight stitches later,
I woke up from my nightmare,
determined to be the
leader in the pack.
This ain't over, Terry.
You know that Jungle
is gonna stitch you up
with that gun.
Take this.
These are the keys
to my apartment.
There's no trace on any of it.
And I've contacted Dutch for ya.
You know what they say
about the land of smiles?
Sun.
Sea.
Sex!
My eyes were
popping out of my head.
I'd never seen anything like it.
If heaven and hell
threw a party,
this is what it would look like.
There was something for
everyone, even chicks with dicks.
Women in bikinis
and enough strobes
to give you a
bloody heart attack.
Dangerous, debauched, and dirty.
And then comes the
age-old chat up line
that makes every man
feel like a king.
Hey sexy man!
Where are you going?
Going to get a drink.
And it works.
I can take you somewhere nice.
You ever been with a Thai girl?
We can have sex all night,
and I make you breakfast
in the morning.
I don't normally
listen to the hype.
But you ain't seen nothing
till you lived a
night in Bangkok.
The next day I woke up late.
It had been a busy night.
I felt like a man reborn.
I left girl inside snoring,
and she never cooked me
that bloody breakfast
in the morning.
She never kept her
side of the bargain.
Anyway, I made my way
through the city streets.
The roads were like
motorways polluted
and rivers of traffic flowing
around in all directions.
I had an appointment to
keep with Terry's contact.
When years ago, they had
a car business going,
a very lucrative one indeed,
stealing cars from
Eastern Europe
and driving them over to
the UK and then selling them
to high-class
businessmen in the city.
Until they got busted of course.
It was time to meet Dutch.
Take a seat, Byron.
So, how's Bangkok?
Yeah, Bangkok's good.
It's a fucking crazy town.
Welcome to Thailand.
Thanks.
You like my place?
I mean, it's Dutch.
Looks good, nice.
I see you got a nose problem.
What happened?
Yeah, I had a few
issues back home.
Only a small problem though.
If you've got a
problem, you come to me.
You wanna have a drink, Byron?
I'll have a beer please.
I ordered some
frikandels for you.
Real Dutch snacks you know.
Try those.
I want you to taste them.
Do you like it?
Tastes good, yeah.
Anyway, enough about snacks.
So, what's your plan, man?
Terry said that you're gonna
be here for while, right?
I'll be here for a short time.
But I got an open ticket though.
Open ticket?
Keep that open ticket, man.
I think you're never
gonna return though.
Ha ha.
It's like a Disneyland
for adults here.
You can shag any
women in any place.
You'll feel like a king here.
You'll be surrounded by
all those pussies here.
There's no escape.
Well, there is.
When the bill arrives,
then they're gone.
Your money as well.
No money, no honey.
Sounds like my ex, you know.
Done the same thing to me,
stitched right fucking kipper.
Byron, look at that
guy behind you there.
You see that?
He's gonna shag
that girl very soon.
I like to watch it.
Like the whole process.
I mean, look at that man.
The marketing is great.
The product is shit.
Back to business.
Don't stick that nose of yours
into any bullshit here, okay?
No worries, no problem.
Don't solve
anything yourself.
I understand.
So, yeah, I have a
few businesses out here.
I mean, I'm always
willing to expand.
Only with good guys.
Like you.
Thanks for the offer.
But as I said, I am only
here for a short time.
You're gonna
love Thailand, man.
Yeah,
thanks for seeing me.
Anyway, Terry told me
to keep an eye on you.
Show me your eyes.
I have a crocodile farm.
I'm a shareholder of it.
I want you to go with me.
- Thanks.
- So, take care, man.
Bye.
It's nice to meet you Byron.
Thank you.
Hey, come on, get up!
Police are
investigating an armed robbery
that took place at 1:00 pm today
at the 6th Avenue
nightclub in Cambridge.
The club is known to be
frequented by known criminals,
and the police believe that
this is a start of a turf war.
Police have linked the robbery
to Byron Harrison,
who is at large.
They have stated he
is armed and dangerous
and must not be approached.
Come on, Byron, pick up.
Come on, Pick up
the fucking phone.
Fucking Jungle!
He's definitely used
the fucking gun.
What?
I knew this would be the day
I regretted the job
I did years ago.
Jungle demanded the
firm silence someone.
Move.
Move!
Shut the fuck up!
The Brazilian Mastiff
is known for its aggressiveness
and impetuous temperament.
It's also a thieving bastard
and will shag your
wife when you're away.
Marcello, where's
the fucking money?
I don't know
about money, guys.
What do you mean you
don't know about money?
I don't know
nothing about money.
Where's the fucking money?
Look at me, you cunt!
I don't know.
- Oi!
- Where's the money?
You got two choices.
Number one, I put a slug in
that fucking head of yours!
Number two, you tell me
where the fucking money is!
Guys, you know what
happened here, no?
Marcello.
My father, my
brother, my sister,
my dog, my cat fuck your wife.
What do you mean fuck my life?
He know!
You have one small
problem, you know?
Fuck my life, or fuck my wife?
Your wife, your wife!
My wife?
Yeah, fuck her.
What the fuck's
he talking about?
He's talking fucking shit.
Fuck with your friend.
Marcello!
Marcello, look at me!
You believe in this guy?
Come on.
Look at his
fucking eyes, Dave!
Can't you see what he's
fucking trying to do?
Look at him!
Don't believe this guy, man.
And never trust
an Australian pit bull
who wants to be the
number one alpha.
Fuck you!
Why the fuck did
you do that for?
Huh?
Did you fuck my wife?
Dave, why would I
want to fuck your wife?
Huh, why?
You believe in this shit.
How old are you?
What's this?
It's your little finger.
You tell me.
One mistake I made
was leaving the gun
for Dave to destroy.
And this how Jungle framed me.
Take this get rid of it.
There's
been a robbery.
It's all over the news.
Have I
been set up, Terry?
I don't
know right now, okay?
It could be a murder wrap.
A fucking murder rap?
You taking the piss?
What the fuck am I
meant to do, Terry?
Leave this with me.
Hey Kate, when are you gonna
get ass out of fucking bed?
What the fuck am
I paying you for?
What the fuck has
she been doing?
Fucking slut!
Fucking bitch.
What's going on?
Where's my fucking
cards and money?
Piss off, asshole!
Where's my fucking cards?
Hey, what the fuck
is going on here, mate?
Got a fucking problem
with the girl or what?
She's got my fucking money.
Do yourself a favor, yeah?
Fuck off.
No!
Where's my fucking
cards and money?
Speak to Joe.
Joe?
Who the fuck is Joe?
Boys Town.
Boys Town?
What the fuck is that shit?
Huh?
Go to Cockatoo Bar.
Who's the wanker now?
Hello, mate.
Yeah, what do you need?
I'm looking for the Cockatoo
Bar, a guy called Joe.
Joe?
Never heard of him.
You sure?
Yeah, sure.
What do you need?
Katie told me you could get
me some cards, some plastic.
All right.
Go straight, second
door on your left.
Thanks.
Yo, that would be our guest.
I've come to see Joe.
So, what can I do you for
in my house of ill repute?
I can get you anything you need.
I can get you Asian,
Caucasian, Eurasian,
Australasian, Afrasian and for
the really truly disturbed,
I can even get you youthanasian.
And of course, there's
the specifics of it all.
I mean, do you want a female?
Male?
Ladyboy?
Tomboy?
Homeboy?
Cowboy?
Playboy?
Toyboy?
Schoolboy?
Atta boy!
I feel obligated to
mention that we have
a two-for-one special
on Manginas this week.
It's a rarity in the market.
So, welcome to Joe's
emporium of sleaze.
Now, what do you want?
Katie told me you
could get me some cards.
Oh, drat.
Here I was, thinking I
was about to get lucky.
Kate you say.
Oh, what a girl, huh?
My top student.
The best ass ever!
My little anal angel.
You need to teach her
to stay to cook breakfast.
She says that to
all her customers.
She's a shit cook anyway.
She'd probably poison ya.
Now, down to business.
You're in the right
place at the right time.
I just received a
bunch of new cards.
And they're from the UK.
This is what we call a
serendipitous encounter.
Really?
Some might even say kismet.
Must be my lucky day.
200,000 baht
and they're yours.
I've got the cash
here with me right now.
But do you ever mix
business with pleasure?
You read my mind.
I have been known to have a
predilection for beastly men.
Are you a beastly man?
This way.
I need to kiss you.
And I like to be the giver
and not the receiver.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
Don't be gentle, darling.
That's fine my me, sweetheart.
It's gonna be hard.
Fuck me like you hate me!
Close your eyes!
Give it to me!
Here it comes!
Fuck, fuck!
Oi!
You motherfucker!
Cheers, mate.
Cheers.
I'm gonna kill you!
Now, you
can beat a dog,
and it's gonna do
one of two things.
One, it's gonna
roll over and die.
Or two, it's gonna bite ya,
Now, I'm the kind of dog
that's gonna bite ya.
I snapped Dutch up on his offer
and we went to his
beloved crocodile farm.
I needed to talk some business.
And of course,
recycle some meat.
Wow, that one's bloody massive!
That's nothing, man.
There's much bigger one's here.
- Yeah?
- Oh yeah.
You know, we feed them steroids.
You what?
Steroids.
In 12 months, they
grow from one feet
to about 10 feet in no time.
We give them double the amount
you normally give to humans.
That's why they're so
fucking aggressive.
Chinese love it.
That's why it's a big market.
Between you and me, ah?
We have the reputation
here of supplying
the best meat in all
of South East Asia.
But come on, Dutch.
Don't they test the meat?
For that yearly test?
Come on.
You see that basin over there?
Yeah.
Those two crocodiles in there.
Those are the ones which
are not on steroids.
That's how we pass the test.
Easy.
All those fucking Yanks and
Aussies, they get big right.
They don't even know why.
Even when you do
that test, you know?
That bodybuilding test.
It doesn't show up;
it's not in the blood.
You eat the meat.
Makes sense.
So how many do you
go through in a year?
10,000.
I'm gonna show you more.
God.
So, Byron, this
is big business.
Over there we have more
than a thousand crocodiles.
Shit, really?
What do you do with 'em?
Handbags, jackets.
Meat.
Mostly we sell to
USA and Australia.
We have a concept here.
Nothing goes to waste.
So even the off cuts we
feed back to the crocodiles.
That's the meat like the most.
Remember that Dutch
snack, frikandel?
Yeah.
Same concept.
Sounds good, Dutch.
You know, I'm into a
bit of recycling myself.
They love it.
Dutch,
I got a problem.
The other night, I
got my cards stolen.
Now I've got limited cash.
I'd like to take you
up on your offer.
So now you want
to take up my offer?
Great.
How you get your
cards stolen, man?
I slept with a hooker.
I got drunk, and she
took everything I had.
You shut up, yeah.
Okay, you report those cards
stolen to the bank, yeah.
get them replaced in one day.
It's solved.
I can't do that.
Those cards belong to Terry
if you know what I mean.
Terry's cards?
Byron, man.
What the fuck are
you doing, man?
You don't know Bangkok, do you?
Tell me that fucking bar now.
I went back there last night.
There was no cards, no money.
But I found out where they went.
Let him talk, you fuck!
You keep going.
She was with some
English sexpat.
He got a bit lippy,
so I knocked him out.
But I found out
where the cards went.
What did I tell you, man?
You should come and
contact me first, yeah?
Look, they won't even
remember me, so don't worry.
Okay.
Byron, I want you to start
working tomorrow, yeah?
I'm gonna drop Mariya off now.
Tomorrow, you come to my
place in Sukhumvit, yeah?
My villa.
See you then.
I have had a girl
with two pussies, man.
Two fucking pussies.
She was sleeping sideways.
I was maybe a little bit
drunk, but I saw two pussies.
I guess you're making
a pretty penny here.
We do, man.
Well if that's the case,
why are we stuck on
a shitty river boat
and we're not driving
around Bangkok
in some nice flashy motor?
We stay low profile, man.
Low profile is
the key, you know?
If a cop see you in a car,
they're gonna pull you aside.
They find all kind of
tricks to get money off you.
It's not good.
Now were free.
Free men.
But don't they need
a warrant for that?
You know the salary of a cop
is about 10,000 baht a month.
You'll see, near the
end of every month,
they get very fanatic, ah?
Making roadblocks,
and it's so obvious
even the people
make jokes about it.
Okay, I understand that.
Yeah.
But if your making
all this money,
what are you doing with it?
I have my investments
man, and more.
And?
Yellow fever.
What's that?
Thai girls.
Asians pussy.
Think you got it
already, Byron, I'm sure.
Maybe.
He's got it.
Looks like it.
Oh yeah, that's clear.
Let's get out of here.
Always watch yourself.
Yeah, man.
You go to the airport
tonight, pick up that girl.
Go Hong Kong two weeks.
Then you go to Korea, got it?
Hey, can I shag the girl?
Shag the girl!
Stay professional, yeah.
Go!
I can't believe it.
Fuck!
You can't trust your
own personnel anymore.
Why Chinatown?
We have an export
business as a front.
Flip flops, umbrellas,
whatever you call it.
Nobody bothers even
to question us.
Blimey, Dutch.
This place.
It's a proper shit hole.
It's deeper than your ass.
Watch your head.
So, here it is.
Oh yeah, look at that.
Perfect.
Here we pack, dispatch steroids.
Slimming tabs, some other stuff.
I'm gonna tell you
about this later.
I can tell you now.
I'm too old to be
packing tablets.
Terry asked me
to help you out.
That's what I am doing.
Tik, can you get us two beers?
You okay with that?
Time to talk some business.
Take a seat, Byron.
So then, Dutch, time is money.
Tell me more.
Okay, look.
I got my network, yeah.
Worldwide.
With dealers and stuff.
I buy the steroids from all
over the place here in Bangkok.
From various chemists.
Customer wires me the money.
I'll dispatch it here.
Simple.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
So, what do you need me for?
I want you...
to expand my business.
You're the right guy for that.
Why me?
Terry.
He told me you made
your crew back home
a fortune, didn't you?
Yeah.
Man, I think if
we work together...
we can be a great team.
Well, I plan on
staying a bit longer.
Tell me more.
Here we go.
These little babies
here are Thai Pinks.
This is five milligrams
of pure Anabol.
Best seller in the whole market.
Weightlifters, competition
lifters, whatever, movie stars.
All of them.
What do you think?
What if I tell you you can gain
10 kilos in 10 fucking days?
Pure muscle.
This is what we feed
to the crocodiles.
And I like it too.
Dutch.
I've been told about this stuff.
It shrinks your balls.
Well, you know.
We have a counter
hormone to balance that.
All right?
Also, some slimming
tabs and stuff.
So, for every problem
we have a solution.
There's many problems
in the world.
That's why we have
a lot of business.
We have many
businesses from now on.
Sounds like a good business.
Yeah, it is.
Well, those counter
hormones, here's one of them.
You need to take them.
If not...
roid rage, heart attacks.
You can even grow some tits, ah?
I had a customer last
time, he came back to me.
Big problem.
He had a left tit
growing, Byron.
Looked like a fucking hamburger.
You won't believe it.
I was shocked too.
I've seen many
things in my life.
But it was big!
And he asked me like, "Why?"
I said, "Well, you didn't
follow my advice, you know?"
You live and learn, right?
He didn't have money for this.
Well.
Then...
All right.
Jimmy.
Where are you now?
Who's walking up here?
There's nobody coming.
My place?
You sure?
What's this, the boys brigade?
You bad man!
I remember you!
Your one of Joe's guys, right?
You know each other?
I had a problem with his boss.
I told you at the
crocodile farm.
You mean Joe?
What's this?
Hello.
Joe's in intensive care
having his stump sorted out.
Yeah?
Well, next time I'll chop
your fucking bollocks off.
And I feed you them!
Calm down.
Joe!
Nah, it ain't Joe!
It's Bow.
Don't worry about bow, you mug.
It's me innit.
You know Joe's got
the DEA in his pocket.
Your fucked!
Okay.
Then bring it on.
I make some Thai noodle soup.
Okay!
You fucked up,
You bring Mariya upstairs
to Mr. Wang's office, yeah?
Thai wives
are known for cutting
their cheating
husbands' dicks off.
I did the same thing to him.
I'll get back to you.
I was in a
city of 8,281,000 people.
The world is a small place.
Six degrees of separation is
the idea that all living things
are six degrees away
from each other.
That quote is right.
Dutch and Joe were
old business partners.
That was until Joe
wanted to go his way.
You remember what I used
to be famous for don't ya?
You crazy fucking bastard!
What did I tell you about
stepping on peoples toes here, ah?
I didn't know you
fucking knew him!
It's good to stir the pot.
Stir the pot, yeah?
Things go from bad to worse!
There's powerful people
going to his place!
This ain't over yet!
Calm down.
You know what?
I did you favor.
I cut his measly little
fucking dick off.
Now you've got a reputation.
Reputation!
Well, here it
is, ladies and gentlemen.
The classic signs of roid rage.
Yes, I make sure
everybody knows about it!
Everybody!
Good.
It's good, right?
You cut fucking
gay Jo's dick off!
Salivating at the
mouth, profusely sweating,
and dilated pupils like
bloody flying saucers.
This roid rage storm will
clear as quick as it came.
Just you watch.
I don't believe it.
You've got some balls, man.
Forget about it.
Let's celebrate.
Come.
Fuck that guy.
It's better
to be a wolf for a day
than a sheep all your life.
I need to get big,
man, I need to get big.
My fucking bird
is moaning at me,
and I need to get
big, fucking big.
So, guys I just
sent you 1,000 quid.
I wanna gain 40 kilos,
otherwise she's gonna leave me.
Can you do it?
So, Dutch
put a leash on me.
And we went on the
straight and narrow.
We created one of the
biggest underground
steroid dealerships
on the planet.
Everything was
smelling of roses.
And the first thing we did
was get down to business.
We set up a chain of high-tech
distribution units the city.
Then we sent out free
samples to dealers worldwide.
Once they were happy
with the stock,
we undercut the competition.
We had some amazing
ways of getting
the gear through customs.
Wrapping the gear
in carbon paper
distorts the hidden object
to avoid X-ray detection.
It's a bit like lead.
But it's a lot lighter
and a lot cheaper.
Now that is Bird.
She was high as
a kite every day.
She loved her fucking job.
She was our number
one packer from Burma.
We took out the ink
cartridges in marker pens
and replaced them
with our own gear.
Teddy bears were good too.
Another amazing way
of sending the gear
was crushing the tabs
in toothpaste powder.
The customers didn't mind it.
They even brushed
their teeth in it.
You know, there's nothing
like a bit of fluoride
mixed with steroids.
Sending it disguised
as vitamins.
We just took out
the vitamin tablets
and replaced it with our
own brand of vitamin C.
Then we just
heat-sealed the lid,
with our high-tech
machinery of course.
For the injectables we
disguised it as anal sex lube.
Our orders were going out
on an industrial scale.
Not only that, our reputation
was beginning to
get known worldwide.
Those steroid freaks were
getting bigger and bigger.
And the bigger they got,
the more juice they needed.
It was a win-win situation.
Now, I'm not talking
bollocks here.
The steroid trade is as
big as the drug trade.
But it's not frowned
upon so much by society.
But in reality, those guys
are drug addicts with muscles.
All right, Byron.
We're gonna need some gear.
What you up to then?
I got a big order for ya.
The euros are coming up.
I need something that's
gonna give the boys
a lot of power and anger.
I'll give
you a horse steroid.
We supplied everyone
from fitness coaches
to biker gangs to football
hooligans to celebrities.
We supplied everyone worldwide,
from Sydney to
Kabul, Afghanistan.
Hey, I'm gonna need you to
send me another hundred,
hundred bottles of testosterone,
like you did before.
- Okay?
- Fantastic.
Send it to my
office here in Kabul.
APO that shit to me
like you did before.
God damn!
These motherfuckers.
All right.
The insurgence just
broke the perimeter.
I gotta go.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Dutch invested in
a chain of massage parlors,
knocking shops, crocodile
shops and a few other things.
I was a bit more modest.
I had money coming in
from all directions.
I bought myself a
couple of condos,
invested in a speed
boat business,
and had my own car dealership.
I have these
Armenian customers!
I need 50,000 Thai Pinks!
Yeah?
And can you make me this deal,
like I buy one, one for free?
I'm sorry, I'm busy, man.
Come on, man!
Look it, I heard you
have this fucking deal
of a one plus one.
I buy one, I get
one for free, right?
Last time, you did that.
Can you do it again?
I have 50,000.
Not 10, not 20,
50-motherfucking-thousand!
Can you give me that?
Let's do it tomorrow.
Okay,
So, deal, tomorrow,
nine o'clock.
See you, man.
Everything
was going great.
But unknown to us, there were
some new kids on the block.
And they were as corrupt as us.
The next day, Dutch went to meet
these so-called
Armenian dingoes.
He'd thought he'd won
the bloody lottery.
The Devil doesn't come to you
with a red face and horns.
He comes to you as
everything you ever wanted.
If something smells like
shit, you know it's bad.
Dutch got his arse
kicked by Somchai,
a Korean ridgeback.
DEA inspector.
A man of few words.
Yes, I'm in the kennels now.
So, whatever happens, don't
go back to that factory.
It's the DEA.
DEA is on it, man, all the time.
So, what you do now,
you go to Sukhumvit 101,
make some deal with
them, work it out.
Don't let me down, Byron.
Okay, man, I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Do your best.
Here, you fucker.
So, I made
myself spick and span
and went to the grooming saloon.
I had an important meeting
with a DEA officer.
But before I left,
Mariya gave me
a very special pair of glasses.
Made in China, of course.
Did I tell you to sit down?
Where's Dutch?
Dutch is locked in a cage
where he fucking belongs.
So how do we release
the dog from the cage?
You boys think you real
fucking cute, don't ya?
Building your little
steroid empire.
You're not paying
your fucking dues!
You also didn't have
a good firewall.
Didn't think about that, did ya?
Untraceable payments
via cryptic currencies.
Steroids...
is a felony.
Your boy's gonna serve some
fucking serious hard time.
New kids on the block, eh?
Snap this fool.
There's nothing on him.
How's your jaw?
Shut up, you wanker.
I admire you.
Big fucking basketball-sized
balls on ya.
You're British, right?
Yeah.
Where abouts are you from?
The Isle of Dogs.
That's cute.
More like Isle of Pussies.
I always admire you British.
So fucking pompous.
So arrogant.
Think you own the fucking world.
But one thing I like
about the British...
is your pound sterling.
"We don't want the fucking euro.
"We'll keep our pound sterling."
That was good, that was clever.
Tell ya what.
I'm gonna make you a deal.
You've got five days
to bring me 800,000...
of those beloved,
British pound sterling.
And then I'll let your
little mutt out of its cage.
No problem.
Minus...
his shit hole apartments,
his stupid fucking
crocodile farm,
his dirty little
soapy massage parlors,
and he's banned
from the Big Mango.
His Bangkok privileges
are revoked.
You what?
You heard me.
Five days.
800k.
Fetch.
Time to go.
Hurry up!
See you soon, Chinney.
Fuck off, you wanker!
Clock's ticking, Byron.
Five days!
Let's cheers to
that, boys, 800k.
No fucking chance
he's gonna get it.
Remember the man who can?
Two years ago, he renamed
me as Jimmy Harrison.
Where there's an English
Dog, there's a way.
I had four and half days to
get back to Connors with 800k.
All right, Terry.
New motor?
Yeah.
And they say crime doesn't
pay, eh?
I'm not staying for
long, only a few days.
I need some weapons.
Tomorrow.
That afternoon, I went
to see my ex-beloved Tracy.
I was going to tell
her a load of bollocks
and spin her a yarn.
All right, Tracy.
Long time no see.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Pleased to see
you too, darling.
What are you doing back?
If Jungle finds out,
he won't be easy on you
like he was the last time.
And you know the Old Bill
are after as well, right?
I'm not worried about them.
I got a new identity
thanks to a friend.
What's your new
name then, James Bond?
I'm back here for
a short holiday.
I've come back to get my cash.
Some things never change, eh?
I haven't got any of your cash.
The Old Bill took it all.
And any little bits that
were left behind you owed me.
You can't take the chip shop
out the girl, can
you, Tracy, eh?
Fuck off.
And now it's time to
pull on the heart strings.
What happened to us?
Listen, it hasn't been
easy for me, you know.
I didn't expect them to
do what they did to you.
I didn't know anything about it.
Well I'm not here to
cry over spilled milk.
What's done is done.
In many ways it did me a favor.
But I'm back to get some
cash for a new business deal.
You're not getting
anything from me.
You used to spend
my money like water.
Well, why are you
here bothering me, then?
Because I still care about ya.
And I wanted to see ya.
You know I've been
living the life of Riley
for the last two years in Asia.
Sunshine seven days a week.
I've got my own apartment.
Swimming pool.
I go to the islands
every weekend.
I'd like you to
come and join me.
But first I need to sort
out some business here.
Well, where you gonna
get the cash from then?
Now it's shit-stirring time.
I buried some cash years ago
with a deal I did with Jungle.
From a robbery.
Where?
It's for me to know
and you to find out.
How much?
Six figures.
You never told me
anything about that.
I know better than that Tracy.
You know that.
And I need you to set up
a meeting with Dodgy Dave.
Why should I?
Because I'm gonna
give you half the money.
Half the money, Tracy.
All right.
He'll be at the old warehouse
at 1:00 pm on Friday.
They've got a scheduled
drop off that day.
He'll be on the second
floor in the toilets.
That sounds like Dave.
Don't forget he's
got jaws of steel.
I'm not worried about that.
I've upgraded, new technology.
I'm gonna give him
an electrifying experience
he'll never forget.
And Jungle?
He'll be home on
Saturday afternoon.
Alone?
Yeah.
And try and find out
where he hid that gun.
What gun?
The gun he stitched me
up in that bloody robbery.
Okay.
I'll try and find out.
I'd better go.
Your chips are shit.
See you soon, darling.
My plan worked.
Never trust your exes.
She went straight
on the dog and bone.
I just got back from town.
And guess who I saw
swanning around the place.
Who, Sid Vicious?
No, my ex and your
ex business partner.
Cheeky twat must have
come in on a fake I.D.
Well he was talking
a lot of shit.
So much for your
insurance policy.
I though you got this sorted
a couple of years ago.
It was.
Did he have to say anything?
Not much.
But I reckon that Northern twat,
Terry, is involved somehow.
Yeah, makes sense.
See ya later.
Yeah.
I'm sorry,
but the person you've called
is not available.
Please leave your
message after the tone.
Byron.
Byron, this is Dutch here.
I'm having a cold Turkey man
from these anabolic steroids,
so...
get me out, okay?
I count on you.
Get your
hairy ass back home.
Byron's back.
Fucking finish
the job this time.
Byron.
All right, mate.
Yeah, I'm good.
Here you go, buddy.
Cheers, Terry.
I owe you one.
Well, you can me one
when you see me in Bangkok.
I've booked my flight next week.
I'm gonna there, so we
can meet up with Dutch
and grab a drink.
I look forward to it, mate.
That'd be good.
I'd better go.
Okay, buddy.
Goodbye.
What did my old man tell you?
Ha.
Yeah.
He said never to say goodbye.
I'll see ya later.
See ya later.
I'm sorry,
but the person you've called
is not available.
Please leave your
message after the tone.
Guess who, Byron.
Ha.
A little doggy always
returns back to its pen.
Jungle was so happy
and so proud of me
when I set your ass up.
But he's too fucking
stupid and too old
to realize I'm the
new fucking alpha.
I'm fucking waiting.
Bring back my sofa!
All right, Terry,
all right in there, eh?
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck!
With the Aussie pit bull gone,
many of the English Dogs
had left the kennels,
and all was left was a
pack of drunken muppets.
I went to see my
mate Harry Horse Piss
and his beloved Sheila.
Harry sold Sheila's horse
piss to the medical industry.
They turned it into a
estrogen replacement drug
for menopausal women.
Made him a bloody fortune.
Now, horse piss is like
CS gas, and dogs hate it.
Tracy could smell that
there was gonna be
a fight in the air.
I was keen to see
if she would choose
the pedigree or the mongrel.
Your supposed to be
watching that camera.
I am.
And like
all chavy dogs,
she loved a bit of
sex and violence.
What am I gonna do now?
I'm fucked now!
Bish bash bosh.
800k of stolen cash done.
His Bangkok
privileges are revoked.
No way.
No fucking way!
I don't believe it.
Byron!
You're back!
Good dog.
Have a seat.
Clear out, lads.
Give me a minute.
Jesus fucking Christ, Byron.
You are resourceful, aren't ya?
Is that what I think it is?
Yep.
Nice bag.
I'll use this for toilet paper.
Don't mind if I make sure.
Well done, son.
Well done, I'm impressed.
You should have
came to me first.
I would have given you a job.
You wouldn't have had all
this bullshit to deal with.
Did my research.
English Dogs gang member.
Armed robberies.
Extortion.
Very impressive.
Instead, now what?
You're fucked.
They're gonna ship you home.
They're gonna lock you up
for the rest of your life.
You'll never see the
light of day again.
We had a deal.
I don't do deals with dirty,
mangy fucking dogs like you.
You fucking muppet.
You see this?
Do you think I would seriously
wear glasses like this?
There's a little camera here.
And my little friend's
on the end of this.
The video will go fucking viral.
Bullshit.
You're bluffing.
Mariya?
Have a word with this inspector.
I'll make you a deal.
I'm gonna give you five days.
To bring me 800,000 used
British pound sterling.
Call your boys.
Tell them to release Dutch.
Bill.
Yeah.
Change of plan.
Cut Dutch loose.
Never mind.
Just fucking do it.
Keep it to yourself.
Yeah.
Now.
You can drop the charges
due to lack of evidence.
I'll expect a call from
Dutch within two hours.
See ya later.
Jeff!
Jeff come here.
We do things your way now.
Don't worry.
I won't let you down.
Make it slow.
I want him to suffer.
Of course.
Do it.
I won't let you down.
Let me know when it's done.
Motherfucker!
While Dutch was
reinstating his territory,
I enjoyed a glass of red wine,
and was joined by a
bitch of some pedigree.
Hairy man.
Where are you from?
This one was clever as the
devil but twice as pretty.
Who wants to know?
A girl who likes...
big strong hairy men like you.
Are you taking the piss?
If you know what is good
for you, fuck off now!
So, I'm Dutch's friend.
Well I'm meeting him soon.
So, you can say hi
to him yourself.
How about...
you and me...
go to have a little fun?
And after that, we
go to see Dutch.
Hm?
Okay.
Let's do this.
My friend, take this.
And...
What the fuck is that shit?
You don't worry.
I am gonna show you
time of your Life.
Look what do we have here.
You could call it a
little DIY project.
But I like to call
it the Transmorpher.
It's made by Euro,
and its gonna screw
your British ass!
If you drink
too many spirits,
they'll hit you all at once.
That's what my nan would say.
She said the same
thing on her death bed.
But she wasn't talking
about the bloody vodka.
It was only later I really
understood what she meant!
Hey Joe.
I got the motherfucker.
I'm getting him ready.
Yeah, you make sure you
bring the money though.
Surprise, darling!
Look at you.
You look like a little
baby, totally defenseless,
just the way I like my men.
I bet you're wondering
what we're gonna do to you.
Don't you fret.
I gonna tell you real soon.
It's a surprise.
One...
Two...
Joe!
Make you a fucking frikandel.
Ah, you got a few scratches.
Come on, let's get a beer.
Now, a
cat has nine lives.
But a dog has 10.
And not all of us can
be the true alpha.
Some of us need to make
mistakes on the way.
Dutch watched on and
enjoyed his frikandels.
He was like a predator
in the shadows.
Connors had a paddy, and
he knew he'd fucked up.
He thought sleeping
dogs would lie.
In life, you gotta
let go of your fears
and chase your dreams.
When you make a
mistake, there are only
three things you should
ever do about it.
Admit it, learn from it,
and don't bloody repeat it.
Mistakes have the power
to turn you into something
better than you were before.
When it's all said and done,
and push comes to shove,
the underdog takes
over the pack.
You gotta recycle the
present to save the future.
Kill them with success and
bury them with a smile.
Now mongrels that
create their own drama
deserve their own karma.
If they stand beside
you, you respect them.
If they stand against
you, you recycle them.
But that's another story
in the dogs days of glory.
I went back to form a
new breed of English Dog.
But first, I had to deal
with a couple younger runts.
You're probably expecting
me to say I found Jesus
and I learned how to forgive,
or I started on
a different path.
One more righteous,
and respected.
But the truth is, fuck that.
You can't teach an
old dog new tricks.
Get me the fuck out of here!
I wanna see a man about a dog!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org